get-paid.com 2014-02-09

# Make Money Online with Get Paid - (GPTreasure)

Please read this privacy policy to learn more about:

  * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by Get-Paid.com.com ("Get-Paid.com") or by third-party advertisers (together, the "Third-Parties" or individually a "Third-Party" );
  * How the information is used;
  * How you can access and change your account information;
  * How you will receive notice of changes in this privacy policy; and
  * How to contact Get-Paid.com.

To become a member of Get-Paid.com, you must register and create an account on the Get-Paid.com website. The only information that Get-Paid.com collects is the information you provide through the Get-Paid.com registration process, and the information you provide when you update your payment options. This information includes your first and last name, your email address, your Internet Protocol Address ("IP address"), and other contact information. Your IP address is recorded when you register, so that Get-Paid.com can enforce its one account per person policy and other provisions of our Terms of Service and Rules. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by Get-Paid.com from the website (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization), and it is exclusively owned by Get-Paid.com. This information can be utilized by Get-Paid.com in such manner as Get-Paid.com, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate. 

In the event that you subscribe to or opt-in a Third-Party offer, Get-Paid.com may provide your information to the Third-Party in order to directly faciliate the relationship between you and the advertiser.

Your email address may also be used for tracking purposes, when you complete offers, so that Get-Paid.com can determine that you completed the offers. Get-Paid.com will also use your email address to send you the Get-Paid.com newsletters, unless you have opted out of receiving such newsletters. You can OPTOUT anytime by going to 'My account', under PERSONAL DETAILS .

Get-Paid.com is committed to protect its users' privacy, and will not share this information with anyone else, beside in the cases mentioned above.

In addition, there are some cases when a user gives out more information than what mentioned above. For instance, if there's a problem with an offer that a user tried to complete and the user needs to provide Get-Paid.com with personal information (such as print screen of an order that he placed). Get-Paid.com is committed to protect users' privacy in any case whatsoever and all information Get-Paid.com gets from its users will be kept confidential.

Get-Paid.com.com ("Get-Paid.com") deals in large part with the Third-Parties. You may be asked by the Third-Parties to give them your personally identifiable information, either when you complete an offer, when you use their websites, or by some other means. Get-Paid.com is not responsible for information you provide the Third-Parties, and you should read their privacy policies as well before providing them with any such information. Please note, unless otherwise stated, any offer you complete on Get-Paid.com.com will be with a Third-Party.

Any information you post on the Get-Paid.com website or send through Get-Paid.com's Message Center may be available to other Get-Paid.com users or viewers of the Get-Paid.com website. Get-Paid.com is not responsible for the information you post on the Get-Paid.com website or for information you provide other Get-Paid.com users, all of which you do at your own risk.

It is possible that Get-Paid.com may need to disclose your personally identifiable information from time to time. Specifically, Get-Paid.com may disclose any information it has about you to legal authorities, your Internet Service Provider, or other harmed parties without your prior permission, if Get-Paid.com has a good-faith belief that such disclosure is warranted and/or necessary because: (1) you have violated Get-Paid.com's Terms of Service and Rules, (2) you have undertaken actions which are illegal, fraudulent, or otherwise harmful to Get-Paid.com, its users, or the Third-Parties, or such disclosure is necessary (3) to conform to legal requirements or to comply with the legal process, (4) to protect and defend Get-Paid.com's rights in any legal, judicial or administrative proceeding; or (5) to enforce the Terms of Service. 

You can review the personal information you have provided Get-Paid.com and make any desired changes to that information by logging in to your account on the Get-Paid.com website, clicking on the "My Account" icon in the "Members Area" section of the Get-Paid.com website, by editing the information, and then by submitting the revised information. You should update Get-Paid.com on any changes that occur, which would make the information you have provided Get-Paid.com inaccurate or misleading.

Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable information may be used or shared will be emailed to you or posted on the Get-Paid.com website. Your continued use of the Get-Paid.com program after such notices of changes have been sent to you or published on the Get-Paid.com website constitutes your consent to the changes.

Unless stated otherwise, Get-Paid.com's current privacy policy applies to all information that Get-Paid.com has about you and your account. If you have any questions or comments regarding your privacy or this privacy policy, you should contact Get-Paid.com prior to providing Get-Paid.com any personally identifiable information.

Last Updated: January 19th, 2012.
